SARFARAZ MOHAMMAD WAZA

Mern Full Stack Web Developer

Solution-driven web developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. I am developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and React.js Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed.





✓ Sarfarazmohammad369@gmail.com



07006410978



SKILLS

🤔 Raipora palhallan, Srinagar, India

WORK EXPERIENCE

React developer

Recimotech Solutions

02/2022 - 01/2023

sinagar

1 year of experience at recimotech solutions as a React.js developer

Front End Developer

FreeLancing

03/2023 - 09/2023

srinaaar

7 months experience in free lancing as a front end developer

ACHIEVEMENTS

B-Tech

I have completed my b-tech in computer science engineering having 7.53

PERSONAL PROJECTS

React Portfolio

Cara E-commerce Website

Hotel Management website

Weather App

Book library

CERTIFICATES

Mern stack web developer

B-TECH in Computer Science Engineering

Core Python

Core Python

EDUCATION

B-Tech

Sri sukhmani institute of engineering and technology

03/2019 - 04/2023

chandigarh

Courses

 Computer Science Engineering

Sri Pratap Higher Secondry School Srinagar

03/2017 - 03/2018

Sringagr

Courses

Medical+Math

Metriculation

Al-Noor Educational Trust

01/2006 - 03/2016

Pattan

ORGANIZATION SKILLS

Attention to detail

Project management

Strategic planning

Task analysis

Lead projects to completion

LANGUAGES

Urdu

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

coding

programming

designing

developing